University Photograph; Collection ua390
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Susan Seabury Smith, New York State College for Teachers, Class of 1935, accepting the Excellence in Service Award during Alumni Weekend, 1977.
- Anthony J. Casale, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1969 and president of the Alumni Association, presenting an award to an unidentified student during Alumni Weekend, 1977. Duplicate of 9899.
- A picture of Vincent O'Leary, Acting President from 1977?1978 and President from 1978?July 31, 1990 at an unidentified banquet-like event, either preparing to give a speech or just finishing one. During O'Leary's administrations, the institution was named State University of New York at Albany from August 1962?fall 1986 and the University at Albany, SUNY starting in the fall of 1986 and continuing. There is an unidentified woman in the foreground.
- Sorrell E. Chesin (viewer's right), Office of University Affairs, serving as the Master of Ceremonies at the Alumni Weekend banquet when Eunice Baird Whittlesey, New York State College for Teachers, Class of 1944, and Immediate Past President of the Alumni Association, installs Antony J. Casale, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1969, as the new President of the Alumni Association., 1977
- A group of unidentified people seated on the dais at a banquet associated with Alumni Weekend, 1977. Duplicate of 9866.
- Participating in the "Hell No We Won't Go" pre-retirement panel during Alumni Weeekend are, left to right: J. Wesley Childers, retired faculty, and moderator of the event; David Hartly, retired faculty member; Hedi McKinley, School of Social Welfare; Warren Scott, College of General Studies; and Lia Catalano, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1971, Office of Personnel Administration., 1977
- Warren Scott, Department of General Studies and Lia Catalano, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1971, and Office of Personnel Administration, participating in the "Hell No We Won't Go" pre-retirement panel during Alumni Weekend, 1977.
- Ronald Schafer, Alumni Director, speaking at an event associated with Alumni Weekend, 1977. To the right of the podium is Lorraine Chesin.
- Ronald Schafer, Alumni Director, speaking during an event associated with Alumni Weekend, 1977. Sorrell E. Chesin, Office of University Affairs, and Lorraine Chesin are seated to the right of the podium.
- Three unidentified men attending the 50th reunion of the Class of 1927 during Alumni Weekend, 1977. Duplicate of 9859, 9680.
- Ann Jamba Ficek, Class of 1954, Karel Ficek, and Kathlyn Andrews at an event associated with Alumni Weekend, 1977. Duplicate of photograph 7099.
- A picture of John F. Yager, New York State College for Teachers, Class of 1959, receiving the Bertha Brimmer Medal from Anthony J. Casale, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1969 and President of the Alumni Association at the time of this photograph. The event is associated with the State University of New York at Albany Alumni Weekend, 1977.
- Anthony J. Casale, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1969 and president of the Alumni Association, presenting the Excellence in Service Award to Susan Seabury Smith, New York State College for Teachers, Class of 1935, during Alumni weekend, 1977.
- Anthony J. Casale, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1969 and president of the Alumni Association, presenting an award to an unidentified student during an event associated with Alumni Weekend, 1977. Duplicate of 9902.
- Anthony J. Casale, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1969 and a one time member of the New York State Assembly, presenting a student award to an unidentified man during an event associated with Alumni Weekend, 1977. Duplicate of 9908.
- J. Vanderbilt Straub, chairman of the SUNYA Council, and Michael Lampert, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1973 and Class of 1973 Treasurer, attending an event associated with Alumni Weekend, 1977.
- Pictured are, left to right: Sue Bryant, Reginald K. Garrett, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1977, and Pamela Boyer, all graduate students at the State University of New York at Albany at the time the photograph was taken.
- A picture of a baseball player hitting a ball while spectators look on from behind a fence. The hitter is a member of the State University of New York at Albany baseball team. There are crop marks in the top and bottom margins., 1977
- Cindy Werner of the State University of New York at Albany women's basketball team, making a foul shot in a game against the College of St. Rose. This photograph has in irregular nine sided geometric shape., 1977
- A picture of Vincent O'Leary, Acting President from 1977?1978 and President from 1978?July 31, 1990, speaking at a commencement ceremony. During O'Leary's administrations, the institution was named State University of New York at Albany from August 1962?fall 1986 and the University at Albany, SUNY starting in the fall of 1986 and continuing.
- A picture of Vincent O'Leary, Acting President from 1977?1978 and President from 1978?July 31, 1990, speaking with a student from the School of Criminal Justice. During O'Leary's administrations, the institution was named State University of New York at Albany from August 1962?fall 1986 and the University at Albany, SUNY starting in the fall of 1986 and continuing. There are crop marks on all sides of the photograph. In the top margin, upper righthand corner is written an uppercase letter "G." and in the bottom margin is written "REDUCE TO 29 1/2 PICAS" (between arrows).
- A picture of Vincent O'Leary, Acting President from 1977?1978 and President from 1978?July 31, 1990, talking to a small group of unidentified people. During O'Leary's administrations, the institution was named State University of New York at Albany from August 1962?fall 1986 and the University at Albany, SUNY starting in the fall of 1986 and continuing. There are crop marks on all sides of the photograph.
- A picture of Vincent O'Leary, Acting President from 1977?1978 and President from 1978?July 31, 1990, talking to two students. During O'Leary's administrations, the institution was named State University of New York at Albany from August 1962?fall 1986 and the University at Albany, SUNY starting in the fall of 1986 and continuing.
- An unidentified student attending a class in the School of Social Welfare at the State University of New York at Albany. There are crop marks on all sides of the original. Written in the left margin is "F" and in the bottom margin between two arrows is "REDUCE TO 7 PICAS." Duplicate of 20071., 1977
- Gerald Dunn, New York State College for Teachers, Class of 1951, and Shirley Wiltse Dunn, New York State College for Teachers, Class of 1950, attending an event associated with Alumni Weekend, 1977.
- Co-Captains of the 1977 State University of New York at Albany football team: Frederick Brewington (left), State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1979, quarterback, and Ray Gay (right), safety.
- State University of New York at Albany football coaches on the 1977 team, kneeeling: Kevin Callahan, fullbacks; Michael A. Motta, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1974, offensive coordinator; Jon Kralovic, defensive secondary; Mike Welch, offensive halfback; Bob Ford, Head football coach; Gary Reynolds, receiver. Standing: Jack Siedlecki, defensive coordinator; Charles (Chuck) R. Kroll, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1978, defensive ends; Paul Adams, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1976, specialty teams; Bill Deviero, defensive tackle; Dean Peterson, quaterback; John Fraser, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1978, defensive cornerbacks; Hank Jauczyk, offensive line; Tom Depalma, offensive line.
- Elaine Drooz Friedman, New York State College for Teachers, Class of 1945, speaking at an event associated with Alumni Weekend, 1977. Duplicate of 9898.
- Ferol Christian Gallagher, New York State College for Teachers, Class of 1917, attending the 60th reunion of the Class of 1917 during Alumni Weekend, 1977.
- Helen Hynes Germer (right, looking at camera), New York State College for Teachers, Class of 1927, and Dr. Arthur Collins (in background), New York State College for Teachers, Class of 1948, participating in events associated with Alumni Day, 1977. Duplicate of photograph 9881.
- A picture of Vincent O'Leary, Acting President from 1977?1978 and President from 1978?July 31, 1990, giving a speech at a commencement. During O'Leary's administrations, the institution was named State University of New York at Albany from August 1962?fall 1986 and the University at Albany, SUNY starting in the fall of 1986 and continuing.
- A group photograph of Vincent O'Leary, Acting President from 1977?1978 and President from 1978?July 31, 1990, with Steve Einhorn, Harold C. Hanson, Esq., Class of 1963, and Alan V. Iselin. During O'Leary's administrations, the institution was named State University of New York at Albany from August 1962?fall 1986 and the University at Albany, SUNY starting in the fall of 1986 and continuing.
- A contact sheet of images of a group portrait of Vincent O'Leary, Acting President from 1977?1978 and President from 1978?July 31, 1990, with Steve Einhorn, Harold C. Hanson, Esq., Class of 1963, and Stanley Iselin. During O'Leary's administrations, the institution was named State University of New York at Albany from August 1962?fall 1986 and the University at Albany, SUNY starting in the fall of 1986 and continuing.
- Attending the Alumni Luncheon during Alumni Weekend, 1977, are: Kay Hotaling, Frank Peper, Mrs. Pat Johnson; Roger Johnson, Sharyn Teves Stuhler, Susan Emborsky, Elizabeth Mickel, Eleanor Metz, and Gail Magaliff, all State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1967. Duplicate of 9919.
- A picture of Vincent O'Leary, Acting President from 1977?1978 and President from 1978?July 31, 1990, with K. (Kirkland) Leroy Irvis, who received an honorary degree at the pictured commencement ceremony. Irvis graduated from the New York State College for Teachers in the Class of 1938. He was the 130th Speaker of the House of the Commonwealth of Pennsylvania -- the first African American speaker in both Pennsylvania and in the United States. He is also renowned as an artist, poet, and scholar. During O'Leary's administrations, the institution was named State University of New York at Albany from August 1962?fall 1986 and the University at Albany, SUNY starting in the fall of 1986 and continuing. There are crop marks on all sides of the photograph. In the top margin is written "to 14_'s" (between arrows); in the bottom margin is written the letter "U" and "46%;" and in the left margin is written "to 13_'s" (between arrows).
- Herman Kleine, New York State College for Teachers, Class of 1941, accepting the Distinguished Alumni Award during Alumni Weekend, 1977. Looking on are: Eunice Baird Whittlesey (standing), New York State College for Teachers, Class of 1944; Sorrell E. Chesin, Office of University Affairs; Lorraine Chesin; and J. Vanderbilt Straub, chairman of the SUNYA Council.
- Emmett B. Fields, President of the State University of New York at Albany (the name of the university at the time of this photograph and was so from August 1962 until the fall of 1986) from July 1, 1975?1977, with contributors to the 1977 Annual Fund, from viewer's left to right - Nahum Lewis, Ira Freeman, Abba Koblenz, Roy McEnerney, and President Fields.
- A picture of Emmett B. Fields, President of the State University of New York at Albany from July 1, 1975?1977, hosting Lt. Governor Mary Anne Krupsak, Kathryn V. Fitzgerald (New York State College for Teachers, Class of 1922 and chairperson of the Annual Fund), and an unidentified woman on a visit to the State University of New York at Albany to discuss ways in which the university might serve as a resource to state government.
- A picture of Vincent O'Leary (third from viewer's left, front row), Acting President from 1977?1978 and President from 1978?July 31, 1990, with a group of Brazilian legislators from the Brazil Congresso Nacional. During O'Leary's administrations, the institution was named State University of New York at Albany from August 1962?fall 1986 and the University at Albany, SUNY starting in the fall of 1986 and continuing.
- Louis R. Salkever, Vice President for Research, attending the Alumni Luncheon during Alumni Weekend, 1977.
- A large gathering of alumni at an Alumni Luncheon held in association with the State University of New York at Albany Alumni Weekend, 1977. The Luncheon is taking place in a building on the uptown campus.
- A large gathering of alumni at an Alumni Luncheon held in association with the State University of New York at Albany Alumni Weekend, 1977. The Luncheon is taking place in a building on the uptown campus. Duplicate of 9894.
- Unidentified alumni attending a luncheon during Alumni Weekend, 1977.
- A picture of Vincent O'Leary, Acting President from 1977?1978 and President from 1978?July 31, 1990, sitting next to a band and with other spectators perhaps at an athletic event. During O'Leary's administrations, the institution was named State University of New York at Albany from August 1962?fall 1986 and the University at Albany, SUNY starting in the fall of 1986 and continuing. There are crop marks on two sides of the photograph and on the image (on the drum) is written "PHOTO 2B."
- A picture of Eunice Baird Whittlesey, New York State College for Teachers, Class of 1944, and Anthony J. Casale, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1969, and a one time member of the New York State Assembly. Whittlesey is speaking as Casale looks on. Sorrell E. Chesin, Office of University Affairs, is partially visible at right. The event is associated with the Alumni Weekend, 1977.
- A picture of Vincent O'Leary (viewer's right), Acting President from 1977?1978 and President from 1978?July 31, 1990, with an unidentified gentleman. During O'Leary's administrations, the institution was named State University of New York at Albany from August 1962?fall 1986 and the University at Albany, SUNY starting in the fall of 1986 and continuing.
- A picture of Vincent O'Leary, Acting President from 1977?1978 and President from 1978?July 31, 1990, giving a plaque to an unidentified gentleman with other people looking on. During O'Leary's administrations, the institution was named State University of New York at Albany from August 1962?fall 1986 and the University at Albany, SUNY starting in the fall of 1986 and continuing. There are crop marks on all sides of the photograph.
- A picture of Vincent O'Leary (center), Acting President from 1977?1978 and President from 1978?July 31, 1990, with two unidentified gentlemen, awarding a check to one of them. During O'Leary's administrations, the institution was named State University of New York at Albany from August 1962?fall 1986 and the University at Albany, SUNY starting in the fall of 1986 and continuing.
- A picture of Vincent O'Leary, Acting President from 1977?1978 and President from 1978?July 31, 1990, giving a speech. During O'Leary's administrations, the institution was named State University of New York at Albany from August 1962?fall 1986 and the University at Albany, SUNY starting in the fall of 1986 and continuing.
- A picture of Vincent O'Leary, Acting President from 1977?1978 and President from 1978?July 31, 1990. During O'Leary's administrations, the institution was named State University of New York at Albany from August 1962?fall 1986 and the University at Albany, SUNY starting in the fall of 1986 and continuing.
- A picture of Vincent O'Leary, Acting President from 1977?1978 and President from 1978?July 31, 1990, talking to an unidentified gentleman. During O'Leary's administrations, the institution was named State University of New York at Albany from August 1962?fall 1986 and the University at Albany, SUNY starting in the fall of 1986 and continuing.
- Vincent O'Leary, Acting President from 1977?1978 and President from 1978?July 31, 1990 (viewer's left), with the Chinese Ambassador at a press conference. During O'Leary's administrations, the institution was named State University of New York at Albany from August 1962?fall 1986 and the University at Albany, SUNY starting in the fall of 1986 and continuing.
- A group of unidentified people attending an event associated with Alumni Weekend, 1977. Duplicate of 9900.
- A group of unidentified alumni at a reception associated with Alumni Weekend, 1977. An accordion player is featured in the image.
- A portrait of Vincent O'Leary, Acting President from 1977?1978 and President from 1978?July 31, 1990. During O'Leary's administrations, the institution was named State University of New York at Albany from August 1962?fall 1986 and the University at Albany, SUNY starting in the fall of 1986 and continuing.
- A picture of Vincent O'Leary, Acting President from 1977?1978 and President from 1978?July 31, 1990, in conversation with students. During O'Leary's administrations, the institution was named State University of New York at Albany from August 1962?fall 1986 and the University at Albany, SUNY starting in the fall of 1986 and continuing.
- A picture of Vincent O'Leary, Acting President from 1977?1978 and President from 1978?July 31, 1990, with two students, reading a book or document. During O'Leary's administrations, the institution was named State University of New York at Albany from August 1962?fall 1986 and the University at Albany, SUNY starting in the fall of 1986 and continuing.
- Ron Schafer, Alumni Director, presenting the prize for Highest Percentage of Class Attendance to Joan Roeder Barron, New York State College for Teachers, Class of 1952, during Alumni Weekend, 1977.
- A picture of Ronald J. Tenaglia (viewer's right), State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1971, as he receives the U.S. Air Force Commendation Medal from Col. Richard Scibetta, 1977.
- Class of 1927 fiftieth reunion during Alumni Weekend, 1977. Steven Thompson and Gwen Simmons, Alumni Weekend Co-Chairs greet Constance Bauman Abraham, Councillor of Class of 1927. Duplicate image of 7029, 9891 and 9893.
- Dr. Edward Sabol, Robert Margison, and Henry Jaked (seated), all New York State College for Teachers, Class of 1937, at a dinner during Alumni Weekend, 1977. Sabol, Margison, and others are standing and appear to be clapping their hands.
- Eunice Baird Whittlesey, New York State College for Teachers, Class of 1944, presenting the Distinguished Alumni Award to John E. Murphy, New York State College for Teachers, Class of 1937, during Alumni Weekend, 1977. Duplicate of 9920.
- Three unidentified women seated at an event associated with Alumni Weekend, 1977. Duplicate of 9907.
- A group of unidentified people attending an event associated with Alumni Weekend, 1977. Duplicate of 9864.
- A group of unidentified people talking during a lucneon or dinner event associated with Alumni Weekend, 1977. Duplicate of 9903.
- Anthony J. Casale, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1969 and a one time member of the New York State Assembly, presenting a student award to an unidentified woman during an event associated with Alumni Weekend, 1977. Duplicate of 7032.
- Anthony J. Casale, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1969 and president of the Alumni Association, presenting an award to an unidentified woman during an event associated with Alumni Weekend, 1977. Duplicate of 9897.
- A picture of Dr. and Mrs. Lewis Welch attending the Alumni Luncheon held in association with the State University of New York at Albany Alumni Weekend, 1977. Duplicate of 9896.
- A group of unidentified alumni at the 50th reunion of the Class of 1927 during Alumni Weekend, 1977. Duplicate of photograph 9882.
- A picture of C. Luther Andrews, recipient of the Citizen of the University Award, being greeted by Joseph and Eunice Baird Whittlesey, New York State College for Teachers, Class of 1944., 1977
- Bob Donnelly and Pat Purcell Ryder speaking with each other at the 25th reunion of the Class of 1952 on Saturday night during Alumni Weekend, 1977.
- A photograph of the "Elder Statesmen" History Professor Kendall A. Birr, Hudson Winn, Bob Stierer, Dwight Smith, and Ed Sargent, participating in an event associated with Alumni Weekend, 1977. Birr is now Professor Emeritus of History at the University at Albany, SUNY and wrote the definitive "A Tradition of Excellence: The Sesquicentennial History of the University at Albany, State University of New York, 1844 to 1994" (Virginia Beach, VA: The Donning Company, 1994).
- Dr. J. Wesley Childers, retired faculty member, attending the "Hell NoƗe Won't Go" pre-retirement panel held Friday afternoon during Alumni Weekend, 1977.
- A group of unidentified people posing for a picture during the ice cream social on Alumni Weekend, 1977. The event is taking place on the uptown campus. Duplicate of 9911.
- A picture of Vincent O'Leary, Acting President from 1977?1978 and President from 1978?July 31, 1990, giving a speech. During O'Leary's administrations, the institution was named State University of New York at Albany from August 1962?fall 1986 and the University at Albany, SUNY starting in the fall of 1986 and continuing.
- Two unidentified students walking on the academic podium at the State University of New York at Albany uptown campus. There are crop marks in the top, right, and left margins of the original. Written in the top margin between two arrows is "Reduce to 14 Picas." Duplicate of 20195 and 2460., 1977
- A picture of Vincent O'Leary, Acting President from 1977?1978 and President from 1978?July 31, 1990 and a female student participating in Torch Night activities. During O'Leary's administrations, the institution was named State University of New York at Albany from August 1962?fall 1986 and the University at Albany, SUNY starting in the fall of 1986 and continuing.
- Karen C. Kirchmayer, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1977, and an unidenfied male on the Mohawk Campus. There are weeping willow trees and a pond in the background. The Mohawk Campus was purchased by the Faculty Student Association in 1965, and sold by University Auxiliary Services in 1984. There are crop marks in the top and right margins. Written in the top margin is "28."
- An unidentified man receiving congratulations from another man at the student awards ceremony during Alumni Weekend, 1977. Duplicate of photograph 9875.
- The SUNYA Jazz Ensemble performing at the Alumni Banquet during Alumni Weekend, 1977.
- Two unidentified people attending an event associated with Alumni Weekend, 1978., 1977
- A group of graduating students attending an event associated with the 1977 State University of New York at Albany commencement ceremony.
- Class of 1927 fiftieth reunion during Alumni Weekend, 1977. Duplicate of images 7074 and 9859.
- Class of 1927 fiftieth reunion during Alumni Weekend, 1977. Duplicate of images 7073 and 9874.
- Class of 1927 fiftieth reunion during Alumni Weekend, 1977. Duplicate of image 7072.
- Alumni Weekend co-chairs Steve Thompson and Gwen Simmons, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1974, during Alumni Weekend, 1977. Duplicate of photograph 7006.
- An unidentified woman making a speech at the 50th reunion of the Class of 1927 during Alumni Weekend 1977. Duplicate of photograph 7071.
- Lucile Stephens, Kolin Hager, and Ferol Christian Gallagher (right), all New York State College for Teachers, Class of 1917, and three unidentified people attending the 60th reunion of the Class of 1917 during Alumni Weekend, 1977. Duplicate of images 7020, 9888 and 9889.
- Class of 1917 sixtieth reunion during Alumni Weekend, 1977. Duplicate of images 7020, 9887 and 9889.